<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE concept PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Concept//EN" "concept.dtd">
<!-- Endeca Concept Template -->
<concept xml:lang="en-us" id="concept_01FC5849F8D44A3CB4DC1ADD32F0BEFD"> 
  <title>Preface</title> 
  <prolog><metadata><audience type="programmer" job="programming"
		experiencelevel="general"/><prodinfo><prodname><keyword></keyword></prodname><vrmlist>
				
				<vrm version="6.0.0" release="2008-02"
				 modification="none"/></vrmlist><platform>All</platform><component></component></prodinfo></metadata>
  </prolog> 
  <conbody> 
	 <p>The Endeca® Information Access Platform is the foundation for building
		applications that help people understand complex information, fostering
		discovery and improving daily decision-making. These applications instantly
		summarize data and content for users -- even for unanticipated requests. The
		Guided Summarization experience leads to unexpected insights in millions of
		everyday decisions, increasing revenue, decreasing costs, and accelerating
		operations. 
	 </p> 
	 <p> The Endeca Information Access Platform is powered by MDEX Engine™
		technology, a new class of database designed for exploring information, not
		managing transactions. The MDEX Engine is supported by: 
	 </p> 
	 <p> 
	 <ul id="ul_6E68AC20A7DD48418260A825F3FD2695"> 
		<li id="li_FD8B240618294ADD923B5F32676EB0A7">The Information
		  Transformation Layer that unites and enriches disparate sources of information
		  while maintaining, augmenting, and even creating structures across the data and
		  content. 
		</li> 
		<li id="li_E16B0D863EE64B1591198041000E6BE2">An adaptive application
		  component library that enables the rapid development of information access
		  applications that automatically adapt to changes in the data and content. 
		</li> 
		<li id="li_445CC9507A5542DFB878898FCDAB7D7F">A Web-based management suite
		  that empowers managers to highlight the right information at the right time to
		  end users through adaptive presentation rules and dynamic pages. 
		</li> 
	 </ul>These essential capabilities are delivered as an enterprise-class
	 platform, with the scalability, reliability, and security that leading
	 organizations demand. 
	 </p> 
  </conbody>
</concept>
